Hello Gas, we are going to talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company. The
quarterly results of this company for 3/23 have been released. So,
how was the result of this company
and whether this company has given dividend
or not, we will discuss about this
in today's video, so keep
watching the video till the end.
Talking about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company, the
result of the company
is presented in front of you. All the amounts have been
mentioned in the results within the legs. We will
compare those results on a quarterly basis. This is the result of the scooter,
this is the result of the previous quarter, this is the
result of the quarter from last year.
Talking about the income of the company here, there
is gross free income, net free income. By
combining many different incomes, the total income of the company is seen. On a
quarterly basis of Rs. 436200000, there has been a
downfall in the income of the company.
Otherwise, compared to the quarterly basis of last year, the
income of the company seems to be increasing rapidly. The
company got Rs.  The total expense is seen to be
₹4848500 (51 lakh). The company's net expense is
seen to be ₹51 lakh, which is on a quarter-by-
quarter basis and seems to be
increasing rapidly compared to the quarter of last year.
Everything else has not decreased. On top of that, if we
talk about net profit, then
after deducting tax and expansion items, the net profit of this company is
seen to be
around ₹35000 (
2003 lakh) in this quarter, which is a
huge downfall in the company's net profit on a quarter-by-quarter basis. The
rest,
compared to the quarter of last year, the company has
shown decent performance. Along with this, the
company has
also paid its dividend of around Rs 4.50, the
recording of which has already been done. So,
definitely
remember this thing, the dividend is already in your bank account from
here, it must have been paid, so
check out YouTube.
You guys should go and see the earning share of this company here, friend.  This company's earnings yield an APR of 7.88,
which
you can definitely keep in mind.
Overall, according to me, the results of this company have been
poor because,
look here, the market expectations from this company
were a little high and the
company has not generated profits as per those expectations. The
rest of the decline in the profits of this company on a
quarter-by-quarter basis has had an impact
here, which is
clearly visible in the company's
shares as well. Today, the
company has broken down at a very important level of
₹1200. Let's
see if this breakdown continues in the coming time,
and you can
see a good level here, the
level of 1111. You
can buy above these levels. If you want to buy at the rest, then
from all these levels, the
levels of 1360, 1416 and 1600 are where there is
communication about
this company. Rest of the levels, friend, General
Insurance  Within the segment, this company
is one of the biggest Moti Malls companies in India, so I feel that
within the general segment, this
company is available here at a slight discount, so
this company can be accumulated here, it is only
for long term purpose, so that's all
for today, goodbye of goodbye, see you
again in the next video, goodbye
and if by mistake you have invested in this company at higher
levels, then do
not send this communication in loss, okay, that's all
for today, goodbye goodbye, see you
again in the next video, good